Zakir Raza

Front-End Developer

Contact

Phone: +92 3293271727

E-Mail: zaakiraza110@gmail.com

Portfolio:

https://zaakiraza.github.io/Portfolio

GitHub:

https://github.com/zaakiraza

Skills

• HTML

- CSS
- Bootstrap
- Git
- SQL
- JavaScript

Summary

Experienced web developer adept in all stages of advanced web development. Knowledgeable in user interface, testing, and debugging processes. Equipped with a diverse and promising skill-set. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate in a team setting.

Experience

Front end Developer- Mar, 2024 – April 2024 GDSC, Karachi

As an Internee Front-end Web Developer at GDSC, my role involved crafting visually engaging and user-friendly websites to captivate both our clients and their audiences. I worked closely with our design and development teams to bring concepts to life.

Front-end Developer - Jul, 2024 - Aug, 2024 NextGenDev, Karachi

As an Internee at NextGenDev, I utilized HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript to develop visually engaging and user-friendly websites that captivated both our clients and their audiences. I worked in close collaboration with our design and development teams to transform ideas into reality.

Education

Bachelors in Computer Science - September 2022 - Present Muhammad Ali Jinnah University, Karachi

Web Development - May, 2024 - Present SMIT Program, Karachi